{"Y":{"answer":["No","Yes"],"question":"does the school have a water source?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"No","stack":"2018","data":[6,30,35,9,34,47,98,11,7,28,30.5],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Yes","stack":"2018","data":[69,64,111,62,69,74,245,7,46,126,87.3],"type":"bar"}]},"EY":{"answer":["Basic","Limited","No Service"],"question":"proportion of schools with basic drinking water from an improved source available at school","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Basic","stack":"2018","data":[58,43,74,45,54,52,199,6,37,101,66.9],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Limited","stack":"2018","data":[4,12,6,7,11,18,26,0,3,24,11.1],"type":"bar"},{"name":"No Service","stack":"2018","data":[13,39,66,19,38,51,118,0,13,29,38.6],"type":"bar"}]},"EZ":{"answer":["Improved","No Water","Unimproved"],"question":"primary water source (improved or not)","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Improved","stack":"2018","data":[62,55,80,52,65,70,225,6,40,125,78],"type":"bar"},{"name":"No Water","stack":"2018","data":[8,33,50,13,35,47,103,12,12,28,34.1],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Unimproved","stack":"2018","data":[5,6,16,6,3,4,15,0,1,1,5.7],"type":"bar"}]},"AN":{"answer":["No","Yes"],"question":"is the water available from the primary water source at the time of the survey?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"No","stack":"2018","data":[16,51,72,26,49,69,143,12,15,53,50.6],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Yes","stack":"2018","data":[59,43,74,45,54,52,200,6,38,101,67.2],"type":"bar"}]},"AV":{"answer":["No","Yes"],"question":"does the school have toilets?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"No","stack":"2018","data":[62,60,81,8,53,87,163,15,42,47,61.8],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Yes","stack":"2018","data":[13,34,65,63,50,34,180,3,11,107,56],"type":"bar"}]},"FB":{"answer":["Basic ","Limited","No Services"],"question":"single-sex basic sanitation toilet","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Basic ","stack":"2018","data":[6,13,37,41,19,15,81,2,6,41,26.1],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Limited","stack":"2018","data":[4,8,18,22,14,12,36,1,4,22,14.1],"type":"bar"},{"name":"No Services","stack":"2018","data":[65,73,91,8,70,94,226,15,43,91,77.6],"type":"bar"}]},"FC":{"answer":["Improved","No Toilet","Unimproved"],"question":"is the sanitation improved?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Improved","stack":"2018","data":[10,21,55,63,34,27,119,3,10,64,40.6],"type":"bar"},{"name":"No Toilet","stack":"2018","data":[65,73,88,8,60,93,198,15,43,88,73.1],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Unimproved","stack":"2018","data":[0,0,3,0,9,1,26,0,0,2,4.1],"type":"bar"}]},"FD":{"answer":["Accessible","Inaccessible"],"question":"accessibility of sanitation source to students with limited mobility","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Accessible","stack":"2018","data":[12,19,48,60,46,26,156,1,8,82,45.8],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Inaccessible","stack":"2018","data":[63,75,98,11,57,95,187,17,45,72,72],"type":"bar"}]},"CF":{"answer":["No","Yes"],"question":"are there hand washing facilities at the school?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"No","stack":"2018","data":[61,71,86,18,68,107,281,15,32,141,88],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Yes","stack":"2018","data":[14,23,60,53,35,14,62,3,21,13,29.8],"type":"bar"}]},"CL":{"answer":[null,"Both soap and water","Soap only","Water only"],"question":"are both soap and water available at the hand washing facility?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":null,"stack":"2018","data":[0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Both soap and water","stack":"2018","data":[7,11,11,25,12,2,17,0,1,5,9.1],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Soap only","stack":"2018","data":[0,0,0,0,0,0,1,0,0,0,0.1],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Water only","stack":"2018","data":[0,0,0,0,0,0,44,0,0,0,4.4],"type":"bar"}]},"CR":{"answer":["No","Yes"],"question":"does the school have a changing area where girls can change and wash safely (private and secure, door and lock and hangers)","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"No","stack":"2018","data":[73,90,137,61,99,118,324,18,53,143,111.6],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Yes","stack":"2018","data":[2,4,9,10,4,3,19,0,0,11,6.2],"type":"bar"}]},"FE":{"answer":["Basic","Limited","No Services"],"question":"handwashing facilities","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Basic","stack":"2018","data":[7,11,11,25,12,2,17,0,1,5,9.1],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Limited","stack":"2018","data":[7,12,49,28,23,12,45,0,20,8,20.4],"type":"bar"},{"name":"No Services","stack":"2018","data":[61,71,86,18,68,107,281,0,32,141,86.5],"type":"bar"}]}}